自從我跑到這，一切都像在過節
Ever since I ran away it's been just like a holiday
我有一次永久渡假的機會
I got to go on a getaway that never ends
上頭這有好多東西
There's lots up here to do and see,
感覺就像個大驚喜
it's like a big round mystery
只有我，不需要其他朋友
It's just me and I don't need my friends
月球是多麼完美，專屬於我這粉色呆頭
The moon is a perfect place for a silly pink pony like me
最棒的地方，獻給 Pinkie
The most amazing place for Pinkie
要是你看得到我，你會知道我滿臉笑容
And if you saw my face you'd know I'm filled with glee
只有我在月球上這麼開心
Nobody rocks the moon like me
我有我要的一切，感覺像給我開得派對
I have all I could ever need, it's like a party just for me
往上看就能看到家園
If I look up I can see my home
從外面看感覺美多了，亮綠地和亮藍天
It looks much better from outside,
it's bright green land and bright blue sky
不曉得我幹嘛呆在那
I wonder why I stayed there for so long
月球是多麼完美，專屬於我這粉色呆頭
The moon is a perfect place for a silly pink pony like me
最妙的地方，獻給 Pinkie
It's the most wonderful place for Pinkie
要是你看得到我，你會知道我滿臉笑容
And if you saw my face you'd know I'm filled with glee
只有我在月球上這麼開心
Nobody rocks the moon like me
只有我！
No, they don’t!
這裡有點兒冷，而且也有點黑
It's kinda cold up here and kinda dark too
看著那顆藍色彈珠，我也有點憂鬱
I see that bright blue marble and it makes me kinda blue
這裡沒有多少空氣，地板也不怎綠
I don't get much atmosphere and I don't get much grass
但就算在太空中，也聽的到我的笑
But even in space, you can hear me laugh
月球是多麼完美，專屬於我這粉色呆頭
The moon is a perfect place for a silly pink pony like me
最夢幻的地方，獻給 Pinkie
The most fantastic place for Pinkie
要是你看得到我，你會知道我滿臉笑容
And if you saw my face you'd know I'm filled with glee
只有我在月球上這麼開心
Nobody rocks the moon like me
(只有我！)
(No, they don’t!)
只有我在月球上這麼開心
Nobody rocks the moon like me
只有我！
No, they don’t!
只有我在月球上這麼開心！
Nobody rocks the moon like me!
(只有我！)
(No, they don’t!)